Clara E. Sipprell Papers
Clara E. Sipprell Papers
- Negatives and proof prints
  - Berresford
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
  - Berrien, Mrs. Price, 1953
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Beston, Margaret, 1952
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Beston, Mr. and Mrs. Henry (Elizabeth Coatsworth)
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
  - Benjamin [unclear if this is first name or last name]
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
  - Beyer, Eugene E. Jr. (199 Sagamore Road, Millburn N.J.)
    - Negatives (Box FB005)
  - Beyer, Mr. and Mrs. Eugene E. Jr. and family
    - Negatives (Box FB005)
  - Beyer, [Eugene E.] Jr. (2 daughters), 1969
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB005)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Beyer, Alison (daughter of Mrs. E.E. Beyer, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB005)
  - Beyers and Roses, 1970
    - Negatives (Box FB005)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Bibby, Audrey
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
  - Bigelow, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Birch - Wathen, 1932
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Birch - Wathen, December[?] festival, 1930
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
  - Birch - Wathen, pageant
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Birch - Wathen, mixed
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Birch - Wathen, proofs
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Birch - Wathen, school
    - Negatives (Box FB006)
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Negatives (Box FB084)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Birch tree
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
  - Birtten, Mrs. C.M. (daughter's wedding), 1941
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Bisgood, Mrs. Elizabeth and Bridget
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Blacksmith shop
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
  - Blair, Wiley Jr., 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
  - Blakely, Elizabeth, 1893
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Bleecker, Mr. William
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
  - Blinn, Edward (grandson of B. Boynton)
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
  - Blinn, Maurice and children
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Blives, Mrs Bruce
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
  - Block, Mr. and Mrs. Edgar, 1954
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Blodgatt, Mrs. John Wood Jr. (Grand Rapids), 1945
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
  - Boepple, Paul, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 74)
  - Boggs, Elizabeth Adair Monroe
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Bogoslovsky, Boris, 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Bogoslovsky, Stiva
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
  - Bogoslovsky, Tania, 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB085)
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
  - Bogoslovsky, Tania, as a baby
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Boker, Alouise
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Bonner, Mrs. Norman and Danny, 1943
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Boody, David (son of Mrs. Edgar Boody)
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Boody, Edgar (family)
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
  - Booth, Bishop [Samuel B.] (of Vermont) and family
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
  - Booth, Theodore
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
  - Booth, Vincent Ravi
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
  - Boström, Wollmar and William (Swedish minister to the U.S.), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB086)
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Boyd, Nancy (Mrs. James)
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Boynton, Mrs. Beulah
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Boynton, Rosen and Edward (grandsons of Mrs. Beulah Boynton)
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Boynton (2 grandsons of Mrs. B. Boynton)
    See also Blinn family photographs.
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Bozorth, Mrs. Richard M.
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brandt, Mrs. Paul, 1962
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brasher, Rex (naturalist, Kent, CT)
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Braver, Arlette (daughter of Jeanne)
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - Braver, Janet (granddaughter of Jeanne)
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Braver, Mrs. Paul and children, Jeanne's daughter Arlette, 1954
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Breen, ----, 1966
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brezhkovsky, Catherine, "grandmother of Russian revolution"
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-01)
  - Bridgman, Betsy and Bobby
    - Negatives (Box FB007)
  - Bridgman, Mrs. Ralph and daughter Betsy
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Bridgman, Phoebe
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
  - Briggs, Randy (son of Mrs. Cluett), 1963
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brilioth, Dr.
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
  - Brinton, Mr. Horace, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brinton, Mrs. Horace, 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - British Embassy, Washington, Lady Lindsay [wife of Sir Ronald Lindsay; either Martha Cameron or Elizabeth Sherman Hoyt]
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brofreck, Flora
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Broodbeut [Broadbent?], Mrs. Ira T.
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brookings, Capt. and Mrs. R.S. II, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - Brooks, Dr. R.R. (Williamstown, Mass.), 1970
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Brooks, Hagel, 1961
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1941
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Brother Benjamin and Dr. Simon
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
  - Brown, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - Brown, Mrs. Eugene T., 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Brown, Horace
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
  - Brown, Jeremy
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
  - Brown, Nan (Mrs. Derby)
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
  - Brown, Major Walter R.
    - Negatives (Box FB008)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Browne, Mrs. Virginia (daughter of Major Browne, Hampton)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Brownell, Edith
    - Glass plate negative (Box 69-02)
    - Proof prints (Box 83)
  - Bruce, Mrs. Morton
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Bryant, Mrs. (friend of Mrs. Roebling), 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB087)
  - Buck, Mrs. Ed Ellsworth, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Buck, Pearl
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives, 1963 (Box FB009)
    - Negatives, 1957 (Box FB087)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Buck, Pearl (pianist Theodore K.), 1967
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB157)
  - Buckley, Mrs. James L. (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Buckley, Miss Priscilla
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Buckley, Mr. and Mrs. Walter, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Buckley, Mrs. William
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Buckley, Mr. and Mrs. William and family, 1946
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Buckley, William (children, Sharon, CT)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Buckmaster, Henrietta
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Buckwan, Miss Ethel
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Budjis, Horace J.
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
  - Bulgakoff, [Mikhail?] (Moscow Art Theatre)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
  - Bulgakov, Father Sergei
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Bultmann, Mrs. [Rudolph]
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Bultmann, Prof. and Mrs. Rudolph
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Bumpus, Mrs. (Rochester)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Burch, Gladys, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Burchfield, Charles E., 1958
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Burdette, Winston
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
  - Burian, Mrs. John
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Burns (son of Mrs. Burns, Kittery Point, ME)
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
  - Bush-Brown, Mr.
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Bush-Brown, Mr. and Mrs. James (Amber, PA), May 1965
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Bush-Brown, Lydia
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
  - Bushee, Mrs.
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
  - Bushee, Perry
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Butler, Mrs. William J. (Grand Rapids), 1945
    - Negatives (Box FB088)
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Byers, Mr. and Mrs. J.N., 1956
    - Negatives (Box FB009)
  - Byler, John, 1958
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
  - Byler, Mrs. John (Londonderry, Vermont), 1940
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cadbury, Dr. Henry J., 1960
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
  - Cahill, John
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Caihcart, Mrs Florence
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Calajaria
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
  - Calcord, Rev. Edward
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Caldwell, Mrs. W.T. (daughter of Mrs. Walter S. Feutori)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - California: San Francisco, Point Lobos, 1929
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
  - California: San Juan Capistrano
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
  - Cambell, ---- (daughter of Mrs. Donald Cambell)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cambell, Mrs. Maury (daughter)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Camp Manum
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB186)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Camp Quinibeck
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB150)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Campbell, ----, 1944
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
  - Campbell, Mrs. C.M. (daughter and granddaughter)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Canada
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
    - Negatives (Box FB204)
  - [Canada:] Chateau Frontenac, Quebec
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
  - Canada: French landscapes
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
  - Canfield, Nat
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
  - Captain
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Carbine, Mrs. (daughter of Mrs. Brown) and son
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Carl, Prince of Sweden, 1938
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
  - Carnavale, Donato V., 1969
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Carpenter, Kate
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Carroll, Gladys Hasty and daughter Sally, 1950
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Carroll, Gladys Hasty
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Carter, Mrs. (Kirkland), 1967
    - Negatives (Box FB010)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Case, Mrs. Frederick W. (Saginaw), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB089)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Cassidy, Mrs. (3 generations)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB011)
    - Negatives (Box FB151)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cekich family
    See also Yugoslavia group: Fedja, Ira, Paul, Ivanoff, Irina, Clara E. Sipprell; Khrabroff photos(Feodor's wife Irina and her family); Helms photos (Nina Cekich's first husband and his family)
    - Cekich, Feodor (Fedja) and Nina
      - Negatives (Box FB011)
      - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Cekich, Feodor (Fedja), still life torso of, and Irina
      - Negatives (Box FB187)
      - Negatives (Box FB011)
    - Cekich, Feodor (Fedja), in costume
      - Negatives (Box 49)
      - Negatives (Box 63)
      - Negatives (Box FB089)
      - Negatives (Box FB090)
      - Negatives (Box FB152)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
      - Negatives (Box FB198)
    - Cekich, Helen
      - Negatives (Box FB012)
      - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - [Cekich], Irina and Nina
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB156)
      - Negatives (Box 51)
      - Negatives (Box 64)
    - [Cekich], Nina I 12 hours, 5 pounds, 13 oz., [Sep 1927]
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina II 1 week, 6 pounds, 3 ounces, [Oct 1927]
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina III 2 weeks, 6 pounds, 8 oz., [Oct 1927]
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina IV 3 weeks, 6 pounds, 14.5 oz., [Oct 1927]; 26 Sep 1927
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina V 4 weeks, [Oct 1927]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina VI 10 weeks, [Dec 1927]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina VI 3 months old, with Irene, [Dec 1927]
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina VII 16 weeks Xmas day, 17 weeks New Years day, [Dec 1927-Jan 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina VIII 4 months, [Jan 1928]
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
    - [Cekich], Nina IX 4 months, [Jan 1928]
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
    - [Cekich], Nina X and XV, 6 months, [Mar 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XI, Feb 1932 [?]
      - Negatives (Box FB131)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - [Cekich], Nina XII 7 months, [Apr 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XIII 8 months, [May 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XIV 8.5 months, [May-Jun 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XV grandparents, 30 Sep 1929
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
    - [Cekich], Nina XVI 1 year old, her birthday party, [Sep 1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XVIII with Irina and alone, 1928
      - Negatives (Box FB071)
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
      - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - [Cekich], Nina XIX Christmas tree, [Dec] 1928
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina XX puppets, Feb-Mar 1929
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
      - Negatives (Box FB195)
      - Negatives (Box FB200)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXI no good, Mar 1929
      - Negatives (Box FB073)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXII, Apr 1929
      - Negatives (Box FB131)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXIII, May 1929
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
      - Negatives (Box FB195)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXIV, bust by Konekov, 1929
      - Negatives (Box FB071)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXVI, 25 Aug 1929
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB072)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXIX in school, Apr-May 1930
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXX, May 1930
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXI in leaves, Sep 1930
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXII, 5 Sep 1930
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXIII Christine, 1930
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB091)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXIV, Apr-May 1931
      - Negatives (Box FB076)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXV nursery school, May 1931
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXVI birthday, Sep 1931
      - Negatives (Box FB076)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXVII flower girl, spring, 1931
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB131)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXVIII summer, 1931
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina XXXIX Xmas, 1931
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB200)
    - [Cekich], Nina with grandparents, Clara, Sep 1928
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 10-11 months, [1928]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 2 years, [1929-1930]
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - [Cekich], Nina, Christine, 1929
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB076)
      - Negatives (Box FB200)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - Cekich, Nina, Mar 1930
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB074)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB152)
      - Negatives (Box FB166)
    - [Cekich], Nina with god father Sergei Konenkov, May 1932
      See also Konenkov, Sergei, with god-daughter Nina.
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 5 years, birthday, [Sep 1932]
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina, Jul 1933
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina (Thetford), 1934
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
    - [Cekich], Nina, Sep 1935
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
    - [Cekich], Nina, Sep 1940
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 1942
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 1945
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
    - [Cekich], Nina, birthday, 1946
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 1948
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
    - [Cekich], Nina and Petey, Apr 1953
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
    - [Cekich], Nina, 1967
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina and grandparents
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB167)
    - [Cekich], Nina, gardening with friend
      - Negatives (Box FB130)
    - [Cekich], Nina, horse and 21
      - Negatives (Box FB075)
      - Proof prints (Box 80)
    - [Cekich], Nina with Topsy
      - Negatives (Box FB131)
    - [Cekich], Nina, Irina
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
      - Negatives (Box FB158)
      - Negatives (Box FB196)
      - Negatives (Box FB199)
    - [Cekich], Nina
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
      - Negatives (Box FB131)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
      - Negatives (Box FB197)
    - [Cekich], Nina (?)
      - Negatives (Box 62)
      - Negatives (Box 68)
      - Negatives (Box FB129)
      - Negatives (Box FB165)
  - Central
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
  - Chaliapin, Feodor
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
  - Chamberlain, William
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Chamberlain, William F.
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
  - Chamberlain, Mrs. William, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Chamberlain, David (son of Mrs. William F. Chamberlain)
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Chambers, Robert
    - Negatives (Box FB090)
  - Chapin, Edith (Manchester)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Chapin, Ellen
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Chatfield, Mrs. (mother of Mrs. George B. Cressy)
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box 63)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Chazeau, Mrs. C.
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Chekova, Olga [wife of Anton Chekov], See Knipper-Chekhova, Olga.
  - Cheney, Bush
    - Negatives (Box FB187)
  - Cherry Lawn School
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
  - Cherry, Barbara
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
  - Chi Chen, 1955
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
  - Child, Mrs. Edwin
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Chinese lily
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Christy, Mrs. E.S.
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Churaevka [village]
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB198)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
  - Church[es], Thetford, Vermont
    - Negatives (Box FB061)
    - Negatives (Box FB182)
    - Negatives (Box FB194)
    - Negatives (Box 58)
  - Churchill, Mabel, 1959
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Clagett, Mrs. E.F. (Saginaw), 1939
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
  - Clark, ---- (father of Eunice)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Clark, Mrs. Franklin T.
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
  - Clark, Dr. Glenn
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Clark, Dr. and Mrs. Harry
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Clark, Mrs. Julian, and 3 children
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB092)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)
    - Proof prints (Box 81)
  - Clark, Katinka
    - Negatives (Box FB091)
  - Clark, Mandy, 1936
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Clark, Russell (children)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Clark, Sally
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Proof prints (Box 75)
  - Cleary, Miss Dorothy, 1960
    - Negatives (Box 49)
    - Negatives (Box FB012)
    - Negatives (Box FB152)